In the last video,
在上个视频中
we talked about why we need a Lambda function,
我们讨论了为何需要 Lambda 函数
and we talked about what that Lambda function needs to do.
并且讨论了 Lambda 函数需要执行什么操作
In this video, we're going to actually implement that Lambda function.
在此视频中 我们将实现该 Lambda 函数
To start with, let's jump ahead and take a look at
首先看看
what the contents of the Lambda function will be,
Lambda 函数的内容是什么
they're included right here.
这些是函数内容
Of course, we need to import any of the modules we're going to use inside of it.
当然 我们需要导入要使用的所有模块
Here, you will see the same review
这个 review_to_words 函数
towards method that we used at the very top of this notebook,
与在此 notebook 的开头见到的一样
and here, you will see the same bag of words
并且这个是之前在此 notebook 中
encoding method that we also used earlier on in this notebook.
使用的相同词袋编码方法
One thing to note is that the bag of words encoding method requires a vocabulary.
需要注意的一点是 词袋编码方法需要词汇表
So, we're going to have to make sure to include that in our Lambda function.
所以我们需要在 Lambda 函数中包含词汇表
Now, we can look the Lambda function itself.
现在看看 Lambda 函数本身
It's pretty straight forward, but I included lots of
该函数很简单 但是我添加了很多注释
comments in case you want to take a look at it yourself.
帮助你理解该函数
At the top here, we have to make sure to include the vocabulary that
在这里需要添加
we created earlier on using the training set.
之前使用训练集创建的词汇表
Then, we need to extract the review that is submitted by the user
然后需要从传递给 Lambda 处理程序的
from the body of the event that was passed to the Lambda handler.
事件主体中提取用户提交的影评
Once we do that,
提取之后
we need to clean up the review by removing any HTML tags and any punctuation.
我们需要删除影评中的所有 HTML 标记和标点
Next, we construct a bag of words encoding of our review.
接着用词袋编码影评
Once we have the bag of words encoded review,
用词袋编码后
we can invoke the end point that we've created making sure to include the endpoint name,
调用创建的端点 记得传入端点名称
and making sure to serialize the bag of words encoding of our review.
并且要序列化影评词袋编码
Once we get the response,
获得响应后
we read it back,
读取该响应
convert it to a string,
转换为字符串
and then for convenience,
然后为了便于阅读
we round it either to one meaning that the review is positive,
将结果四舍五入到 1 表示影评是正面的
or zero meaning the review is negative.
或四舍五入到 0 表示影评是负面的
Lastly, we return the result to whoever called us.
最后 将结果返回给调用者
So, how do we actually go and set this up?
那么如何设置该函数呢？
Well, there are two things we need to do.
我们需要完成两项任务
In addition to creating a Lambda function itself,
除了创建 Lambda 函数本身外
we need to give that Lambda function permission to use a SageMaker endpoint.
我们还需授予该 Lambda 函数 SageMaker 端点的使用权限
So, let's set up a new role that our Lambda function will have.
我们将为 Lambda 函数设置一个新的角色
To do that, we go back to the Amazon console,
切换到 Amazon 控制台
and we scroll all the way down to security identity and compliance,
一直向下滚动到“Security, Identity and Compliance”部分
and click on IAM.
点击“IAM”
Our goal is to create a new role for our Lambda function.
我们想要为 Lambda 函数新建一个角色
So, on the left-hand side,
所以在左侧
we click on "Roles," and then we click on
点击“Roles”
the "Create role" button because we'd like to create a new role.
然后点击“Create role”按钮 因为我们要新建一个角色
Now, our new role is going to be for a Lambda function.
这个新角色针对的是 Lambda 函数
So, we select Lambda function under the service that we'll use this rule,
所以选择 Lambda 函数 在此服务下我们将使用该角色
then we click on next.
然后点击“Next”
Now, what permissions do we want to give our Lambda function?
我们要授予该 Lambda 函数什么权限？
Well, we want to give it access to SageMaker.
我们希望它能访问 SageMaker
So, if we type SageMaker into the search bar,
所以在搜索栏里输入 SageMaker
and then scroll down,
向下滚动
you will see SageMakerFullAccess.
你将看到 SageMakerFullAccess
Make sure to click on the check box to the left to include
点击左侧的复选框
the SageMakerFullAccess permissions to this role.
使此角色具有 SageMakerFullAccess 权限
Click on "Next," and now we need to give this role a name.
点击“Next” 现在需要设定一个名称
I'm going to call mine LambdaSageMakerRole to remind me
我设为 LambdaSageMakerRole
that this is a role for Lambda that provides access to SageMaker,
表示这个角色针对的是 Lambda 函数 并且能够访问 SageMaker
and we click on "Create role," the role will be created for us.
点击“Create role”就创建了该角色
Great. So, that's the first step.
好的这就是第一步
We've now set up a role for our Lambda function to have.
我们为 Lambda 函数设置了一个角色
Now, we need to set the Lambda function up itself.
现在需要设置 Lambda 函数本身
If we again go back to the main Amazon console.
回到 Amazon 主控制台
In this time under Compute,
在 Compute 下
we click on "Lambda," we can create a new Lambda function.
点击“Lambda”我们可以新建一个 Lambda 函数
We would like to start from scratch,
我们将从头开始创建
and we need to name our function.
需要命名该函数
I'm going to call mine sentiment_lambda_function.
我称之为 sentiment_lambda_function
Since we're using Python in this course,
因为我们在这门课程中使用 Python
we need to make sure to set the runtime to Python 3.6.
所以将运行时设为 Python 3.6
Lastly, we need to give this lambda function or role.
最后 需要为此 Lambda 函数设定一个角色
Of course, we want to use the role that we just created.
我们要使用刚刚创建的角色
So, we leave this at choose an existing role,
所以这个保留为“Choose an existing role”
and then we choose the role that we created from this drop down menu here.
然后从这个下拉菜单中选择我们创建的角色
Now clicking on "Create," our Lambda function has been created.
点击“Create”即创建了 Lambda 函数
If you scroll down,
向下滚动
we can see the code for our Lambda function.
可以看到 Lambda 函数的代码
Currently, it doesn't do much at all.
目前里面没有太多代码
However, if we go back to the notebook,
切换到 notebook
scrolling down, we can copy and paste the function that I've provided here.
向下滚动并复制粘贴这段函数代码
So, we select it, copy and paste.
选择代码 然后复制粘贴
Remember, there are two things that we need to add to this Lambda function.
我们向此 Lambda 函数添加两项内容
The first is the name of the endpoint that we've deployed.
首先是部署的端点的名称
Heading back to the notebook,
回到 notebook
remember that we can get the name of the endpoint by typing xgb_predictor.endpoint.
可以通过输入 xgb_predictor.endpoin 获取端点的名称
So, if we copy this and paste it over here,
将这个名称复制粘贴到这里
now our Lambda function knows which end point to use.
现在 Lambda 函数知道要使用哪个端点了
The second thing we need to add here is the vocabulary object.
第二个要添加到这里的是词汇表对象
Going back to our notebook,
回到 notebook
we can print the vocabulary so that we can copy it and paste it into the Lambda function.
我们可以输出词汇表 然后将其复制粘贴到 Lambda 函数里
Once we've done that, click on "Save."
复制后 点击“Save”
So, currently our Lambda function has been set up.
现在 Lambda 函数已经设置好了
Let's create a test event to test it.
我们创建一个测试事件测试下
In the drop-down menu right here where it says "Select a test event",
在这个“Select a test event”下拉菜单中
click on "Configure test events."
点击“Configure test events”
This is how you can add a new one.
这样就可以添加新的测试事件
We wanted to create a new test event,
我们想创建一个新的测试事件
and our event template scrolling all the way up to
在事件模板列表中滚动到顶部
the top is going to be API Gateway AWS proxy.
选择 API Gateway AWS Proxy
Our event name is just going to be testEvent.
事件名称为 testEvent
As you can see, our test event is going to send a whole bunch
可以看到 测试事件会向 Lambda 函数
of data to our Lambda function,
发送大量数据
but the only bit of data that our Lambda function cares about is the body entry,
但是 Lambda 函数唯一关心的是 body 条目
which we are going to replace with a review we wish to send our Lambda function.
我们将其替换为要发送给 Lambda 函数的影评
So, let's plug in a very simple example review.
我们代入一个简单的示例影评
Lets just say, "The movie was horrible."
例如“The movie was horrible.
I do not recommend this at all.
I do not recommend this at all.”
Clicking on create will then create this test event.
点击“Create”将创建这个测试事件
Now that this test event has been selected,
这个 testEvent 被选中后
I can click on "Test," and the result is zero,
点击“Test” 结果是 0
meaning that my model thinks that the review I entered was negative.
表明模型认为我输入的影评是负面的
So, so far so good,
到目前为止一切顺利
our Lambda function is working.
Lambda 函数能正常运行
However, how do we get our website to use it?
但是如何让我们的网站使用它？
Well, we're going to have to create our own endpoint using API gateway,
我们需要使用 API Gateway 创建我们自己的端点
and that's what we'll do in the next video.
下个视频会讲解